-What are you doing? -I reorganized the fridge.
你在做什么？ 我重新整理过冰箱
See? Bottom shelf, meats and dairy.
最底下放肉跟奶制品
Middle shelf,fruits and vegetables.
中间放水果蔬菜
And top shelf,expired products.
最上面放过期食物
Why are you doing this?
你吃饱撑着啊？
Because I'm bored out of my mind.
因为我无聊到快抓狂了
I've already been to the bank, post office and dry cleaners.
我已经去过 银行、邮局、干洗店
Dude,you just described seven days' worth of stuff.
老兄，你做完我一周的工作
Spread it out a little. Haven't you ever been unemployed?
你要放轻松一点 难道你从来没失业过？
I'm not unemployed. I'm on sabbatical.
我不是失业 只是进修中（有安息之意）
Hey,don't get religious on me,okay?
少跟我传教
A guy in your position needs to be better at relaxing.
你应该练习放轻松
That's why we have comfortable chairs. Here,sit down.
不然我们家怎么会有安乐椅？ 过来…坐下
Ready? Watch.
准备好没？仔细看了
And then....
然后…真好
-So,what? We just sit? -Oh,no,no.
就光坐着？ 当然不是
We're not gonna just sit. Watch.
不只是坐着 看好了
-Hello,Chandler Bing. -Hello,Mr. Bing.
我是钱德宾 宾先生
I love you.
我爱你
All right,whoever this is, stop calling me!
不管你是谁，别再打了
It's been 6 months! It's not funny!
你已经骚扰我半年 一点也不好笑
I can see you, Mr. Bing.
宾先生，我看得到你
You look sexy in your new suit.
你穿新西装真性感
Leave me alone! For the love of God, leave me alone!
求你行行好，别再骚扰我了
And that's Wednesday.
这只是周三的乐子
The One with The lnappropriate Sister
本集播出：“情比兄妹深”
rainystar压制iPod-MP4
Hey,you guys! Guess what?
告诉你们
The British are coming?
英国人要打来啦？
Oh,you and your ways.
你的笑话真冷
Since it's Christmas, I'm going to be collecting donations.
耶诞节快到了 我要负责去乐捐募款
I have my bell and later on I get my bucket.
我已经拿到铃铛 过几天就能拿到募捐筒
I'll be spreading joy to the people.
我要散播欢乐给大家
Last year I spread a little joy, but not enough.
去年散播的不够多
So this year I'm doing the whole city.
今年一定要让全纽约 都感受到
I knew a girl in high school who did that. She was very popular.
我有个高中同学也跟你一样 她很红
It's weird,you're starting to sound a lot like Chandler lately.
怪了，你口气跟钱德越来越像
That is so not true.
胡说八道
So,Phoebe,where are you doing your bell-ringing?
菲比，你要去哪里摇铃？
They gave me a great spot right by Macy's.
我分到梅西百货旁当红位子
They never give a good spot to a rookie...
新人很少分到这位子
...but I'm the only one who can say "Merry Christmas" in 25 languages.
可是只有我会用25种语言 说耶诞快乐
I lied!
我唬人的
Oh,my God. Here's Danny.
天啊，丹尼在那边
Just watch this.
你们看
See? Still pretending he's not interested.
看见没？还在假装对我没兴趣
He's coming over. Pretend we've forgotten who he is.
他走过来了，大家装不认识他 忘记他是谁
-Hey,guys. -Hey,Danny.
你们好 丹尼
Oh,Danny! Hey!
丹尼
You know Rachel. She's nice. She's not bad to look at,right?
丹尼，你认得瑞秋吧 她人很好，长得也不赖吧？
Thanks,Mon.
谢了，摩妮卡
Of course.
当然啦
Do you want to go out on a date with her?
你要不要跟她约会？
Absolutely. Is Friday okay?
好啊，周五可以吗？
Friday is perfect. She can't wait.
非常好，她等不及要赴约
On the date,I'll be able to talk to her directly?
约会时 我可以直接跟她说话吧？
See you Friday.
周五见
Okay,what the hell was that? You know what? Don't answer me.
你搞什么？ 算了，不用说了
I have a date with Danny!
我要跟丹尼约会咯
All right,it's 4:30, I guess my lunch break is over.
已经4点半，午休该结束了
-What are you guys gonna do? -lf you're going back to work...
你们等下要干么？ 既然你要回去上班
...I'll probably just hang out. You know,make some calls.
我们大概一起打几个电话吧 真不错
How could I not get the part?
我怎么会落选？
The play was about a 29-year-old ltalian actor from Queens!
主角就是出身皇后区的 29岁意大利演员
Well,Talia Shire suddenly became available.
泰莉雅雪儿突然有空
She's a woman!
她是欧巴桑耶
What can I say? She nailed it!
你要我说什么？ 人家就是有办法
Is there anything else?
好吧，还有什么戏份？
You'll just say no again,but...
你一定又会拒绝…
...gay porn?
同性恋A片？
Happy holidays!
佳节快乐
Feliz Navidad!
耶诞快乐（西班牙文）
Allo and Merry Christmas!
嗨（法文），耶诞快乐
Oh,thank you,sir! Here's some joy.
谢谢你，祝你幸福
-How's it going? -It's going okay.
我来看看你做得如何 很顺利
Good. Let me help you out.
那好，我顺便捐点钱
Oh,thanks!
谢谢 甭客气
Is that a new suede jacket? It looks really expensive.
新的鹿皮外套？好像很贵
Yeah. I guess.
是不便宜
Just get your nails done?
你刚去做指甲？
Yes,Phoebe,but this is all I have,okay?
对，我只剩这些钱了
Thanks. Happy holidays! Here's your joy.
谢啦，佳节快乐，祝你幸福
Thank you! Happy holidays and Wait.
谢谢，佳节愉快 等等
-You can't take money out. -I'm making change for the bus.
只能捐钱不能拿 我跟你换零钱搭公车
Can't you leave the dollar for the poor?
拿零钱就好 其他钱是要救济穷人的
I'm poor. I gotta take the bus.
我就是穷人，而且还得搭公车
Okay,season's greetings and everything, but still
佳节愉快，可是你不能…
Bite me, blondie!
咬我啊，小妞
I'm going to give him something besides joy. Just
除了祝他幸福，我还要…
I can't believe I didn't get that part.
那个角色根本就是为我而写 结果我竟然落选
I'm sorry,man.
很遗憾
What you should do...
你知道该怎么做吗？
...is make something happen for yourself.
你要自己创造机会
You know, like write a play.
例如写个电影剧本
Or a movie. What about those Good Will Hunting guys?
或者拍部电影 就像“心灵捕手”那两个
Be realistic,you know? If I did write something...
罗斯，少作白日梦了 就算我写出剧本
...what are the chances I could get those guys to star in it?
哪有办法请到他们？
Wait a second. I could star in it!
有了，我可以自己主演
Or that.
也可以
I can't write. I mean,I'm an actor.
我不会写剧本 我是演员
I could act like a writer. Here....
我可以装成编剧
But see? Nada.
不过…什么也写不出来
I don't have the discipline that it takes. I can't do it.
我不像编剧一样有纪律 我办不到
I'll help you.
我可以帮你
Yeah. I'll make up a schedule and make sure you stick to it.
帮你订出时间表 盯着你乖乖照做
Plus,it'll give me something to do.
我自己也有事做了
You'd do that for me? Thanks.
真的？你愿意帮我？
We'll start slow. All you have to come up with tonight...
对 谢谢 一开始慢慢来 今晚之前...
...is the name of your main character.
...只要想好主角名字
-Done. -And it can't be Joey.
好了 不可以是乔伊
-It's not. -Or Joseph.
不是 也不能是约瑟夫
What's up?
你怎么啦？
I just saw Danny on the subway with a girl...
我刚看到丹尼跟女生搭地铁
...and he had his arm around her.
他还搂着她
Honey,I'm sorry.
我真为你难过
You should be. This is all your fault.
你的确该难过，一切都要怪你
You meddled in our relationship!
谁叫你插手我们的感情世界
You had no relationship!
你们根本没在一起
But I was doing my thing and everything...
不过我已经拟好计划
...was going according to the plan!
一切都按部就班进行中
Oh, God, stop with the plan!
拜托 别再提你的鸟计划
So what if you saw him with a girl?
你看到他跟女生在一起又如何
That doesn't mean anything.
那不代表什么
You'll go out with Danny and be so charming he'll forget all about...
你就快跟丹尼约会 到时你可以火力全开
...that stupid subway girl.
迷得他忘记地铁那个蠢妞
She was kind of stupid.
那女生的确傻里傻气
You're right. I'm just going to go on the date.
你说得对 好，我就去约会
I'm just going to go on the date. That is the new plan.
我会去赴约 这就是我的新计划
Hurry!
快点
-How do you spell "suspicious"? -Why?
“多疑”怎么写？ 干嘛？
I think this character is going to be suspicious about stuff.
因为这个角色很“多疑”
Yes!
帅！
Chandler Bing, seven! Chandler Bing, zero!
钱德宾7分，钱德宾0分
You're driving me crazy with that.
看你玩那个都快让我抓狂了
-I'll stop. -Don't stop.
我不玩就是了 继续玩
Move the bowl further away. Ross could make that shot.
碗拿远一点 连罗斯都投得进
Well, you suck. But at least you suck at a man's game now.
真是逊毙了 不过至少你进了成人组
-Want to play? -I can't play games.
要不要玩？ 我不能跟你玩
Ross'll be home soon. I have to write five pages to stick to his schedule.
罗斯就快回来了 按照他的时间表 我应该写完5页
So play for 30 minutes, then write until he gets home.
你可以先玩30分钟 再继续用功到他回家
All right.
好吧
But listen,what do you say we...
不过
...crank it up a notch?
规则应该更困难
I'm intrigued.
愿闻其详
All right. All we need is a little lighter fluid.
要先找到可燃性液体
But be careful. I want our security deposit back.
好，不过你小心点 我还想拿回房租押金
We said goodbye to that when we invented hammer darts.
我们发明铁锤标枪时 就拿不回来了
Do you even remember which part of the wall is not spackle?
你记得哪面墙壁没补过吗？ 记得，这里
Thank you! Happy holiday.
谢谢，佳节愉快
No,that's trash,young lady. You can't
小姐，那可是垃圾，不可以…
Stop that young lady! She donated trash!
别这样，小姐，她竟然捐垃圾
The charity's on fire!
乐捐筒着火了
Help! Thank you. I need that!
来人啊 谢谢，我正需要
What is this?
那是什么鬼东西？
It's 9:00 in the morning!
现在才早上9点耶
All right. "A room."
我看看，场景，房间
"A man enters. He looks suspicious."
一名男子满脸狐疑地走进来
That's it?
就这样？
You're supposed to have five pages done by now...
乔伊，你今天应该写5页
...including an exciting incident.
还包括一个高潮
What is all this? "The Official Rulebook of Fireball."
这是什么垃圾？ 大火球游戏规则
That's the game we played.
我们刚在玩这游戏
It's great. You take a tennis ball,a bowl and lighter
很好玩，道具就是一颗网球 一个碗、可燃液体
This is helping your career? You wanted to be an actor.
这对你的事业有帮助吗？我还以为你想当演员
Not the creator of "Crazy Lawsuit Game."
不是发明危险游戏被人告
You're right. I'll get back to work.
你说得对，我该工作了
Shame on you! You should know better! Joey needs to work.
你真不应该，还带坏他 明知道乔伊应该要工作
Now come on.
振作点
You can have this back when the five pages are done.
等你写完5页才还你
-I had a nice time tonight. -So did l.
我今晚很开心 我也是
I'm really glad Monica asked us out.
幸好摩妮卡约我们出来
I'd love to ask you in, but my sister's visiting.
我很想请你进去 不过我妹来住我家
-I think she's asleep on the couch. -Your sister?
她可能睡在沙发上了 你妹妹？
Your sister's asleep on the couch?
睡在沙发上？
I saw you with her on the subway and now she's asleep on the couch!
我上次看到你们搭地铁 现在她还睡在你沙发
-I thought I heard you. -Hey,great,you're up.
我就猜是你 太好了，你起床了
Rachel,my sister Krista.
瑞秋，这是我妹妹克莉丝塔
Nice to meet you.
很高兴认识你
I wish you'd warned me. I'd have fixed myself up.
你应该告诉我要带朋友回来 害我穿得邋里邋遢
-Like it would help. -You are so bad.
有差吗？ 你真恶劣
-You are. -You are.
你才是 是你
-You are. -You are!
是你 是你
You are so dead.
你完蛋了
I'm gonna get you. Come here!
我要教训你一顿
It's very nice to meet you.
很高兴认识你
Nobody! Nobody respects the bucket!
没有人，没一个人尊重募捐筒
You wouldn't believe what people put in here!
大家都丢些莫名其妙的东西
Does this look like a garbage can to you?
你觉得这像垃圾桶吗？
Does it look like an ashtray?
不像 像烟灰缸吗？
Does it look like a urinal?
不像 像尿桶吗？
-So you going back out there? -Yeah, but I won't take any more crap.
菲比，你还要回去募捐吗？ 当然，不过我受够了
No more Mrs. Nice Bucket.
再也不当募捐好好小姐
Good. You're tough. You lived on the street.
加油，你在街上流浪过，够悍
I'll go back to being Street Phoebe.
我要当回强人菲比
But not totally back. Street Phoebe wouldn't be friends with you guys.
不过也不能一模一样 否则才不会鸟你们 抱歉啦
Can I ask you guys something?
可以问个问题吗？ 当然
I don't have brothers,so I don't know, but did you guys wrestle?
我没有兄弟，实在不沤 你们会打来打去吗？
-Oh,yeah. -All the time.
当然会 常常
In fact,I was undefeated.
而且我从没输过
Well,you weighed 200 pounds.
因为你以前90多公斤
Still,I was quick as a cat.
不过我还是跟猫咪一样矫捷
I met Danny's sister yesterday.
我昨天碰到丹尼的妹妹
-That was the girl on the subway. -You're kidding.
就是跟他一起搭地铁的那个 真的假的？
They were very,you know...
他们非常…
...wrestle-y.
...会扭打
But I guess that's normal?
这样正常吗？
We don't wrestle now.
我们现在不会这样了
Not since I got too strong for you.
自从我长大变壮后就不打了
Too strong for me?
长大变壮？ 对
You wanna go right now?
你要比划一下吗？
I'll take you right now,buddy! You wanna go?
我可以立刻打败你，信不信？
Oh,fine.
没问题
Ready?
预备
Wrestle!
开始
Okay,you know what?
这个嘛…很好
Actually,that helps a lot. Thanks.
谢谢你们帮了大忙
Let's go! The puck drops in 20 minutes!
赶快走，20分后就要开打了 乔伊，快点
Joey's not going.
乔伊不能去
I didn't finish my five pages.
我还没写完5页
Finish them tomorrow.
明天再写不就成了？
Tomorrow he's redoing yesterday's pages.
因为他明天要修改昨天的5页
Yesterday's pages did not reflect my best work.
我昨天写的有待改进
Cut him some slack. If he relaxes, he'll get some work done.
别再逼他，让他透口气 搞不好会写得更好
I think he's been relaxing enough, thanks to you...
他已经透够多气了 这都要感谢你跟...
...and Fireball.
...大火球
If you think Fireball's relaxing, you've never played.
玩大火球可是很紧张 显然你没玩过
You're doing this because you're bored.
你拼命压榨乔伊 是因为你自己没事做
It's not his fault you're unemployed.
又不是乔伊害你失业的
I am not unemployed. I'm on sabbatical!
我不是失业，只是进修中
Guys,don't fight.
你们别吵架
And I'm doing this because I am Joey's friend.
我之所以这么做 是因为我是乔伊的朋友
If you were a friend, you'd be doing the same.
如果你也是他朋友 就该学学我
So being a friend means being a jerk?
当朋友就得这么混帐？
If it does,then you're an amazing friend of mine.
要是真如你所说 你可真是我第一号好友
Let's settle this over a game of Fireball.
别吵了，大家玩场大火球 别气了
-I'll unhook the smoke detectors. -Let's settle this right now.
我去拆掉防火警铃 现在就一了百了
There. Now no one's going to the game.
好了，谁也不准去
-I paid for those! -You said you would,but you didn't.
门票是我买的 才怪，你每次都说要付钱 却一次也没吐过钱
Oh,yeah.
也对
We finally get to the top of the mountain...
我们终于爬到山顶
...and airhead here forgets the camera.
结果这个笨蛋竟然忘了相机
The same thing happened to me one time.
我也发生过这种事情
When did that happen to you?
什么时候？
Remember? We were jogging and saw that bird.
上次我们不是到公园慢跑 看到小鸟
I wanted to take a picture, but I didn't have my camera.
我想拍下来 竟然没带相机
Chasing the churro guy is not jogging.
也对，不过追小贩可不算慢跑
Oh,this is so good. You have got to try it.
超好吃，你一定要吃一口
-Damn. I got it on my pants. -Here,I'll get it.
糟糕，裤子沾到了 我来擦
We better take them off or the stain will set.
最好上楼换件裤子 否则以后洗不掉
-I want to wear them tonight. -Oh,great.
而且我今晚约会还要穿 真好
Okay, bye. Oh,my God!
再见，天哪
-That was unbelievable. -See? I told you.
不可思议 看吧，我早说过了
Yeah. Sorry.
可怜的瑞秋
I don't believe they're brother and sister.
我不相信他们是兄妹
They're brother and sister?!
他们是兄妹？
I guess you'll have to cancel your date.
看来你得取消约会了
And call their mother.
而且还要打电话给他们老妈
“非尿桶”
“我没有百货公司简介”
Wait a minute. Open your hand. Let me take a look.
等一下，手张开给我检查
Quarter,dime. Lint? Not interested in that.
两毛五、一毛、线头？不要
What's this? A Canadian coin?
这是什么？加拿大硬币？
Get out of here!
滚
No drinks near the bucket.
不准在募捐筒旁边喝东西
Set it down there and then you can make a contribution.
先放在那边才准捐款
You can leave the "hurt bunny" look over there too.
少装一副可怜兮兮的样子
Hi,Bob.
嗨，鲍柏
I thought I told you to get out of here!
不是叫你滚了吗？
Phoebe,we've been getting complaints.
菲比，我们接到申诉
-We're moving you to a less high-profile spot. -What？
上面要调你离开 什么？
-Ginger's taking this corner. -That chick can't handle my corner.
以后这里由金杰负责 这小妞才没这能耐
Look, either you leave or we remove you.
你不走，我们就得赶你走
Fine.
好
I'll give you one pointer. Look out for that bitch.
劝你一句，注意那个臭婆娘
-I thought we said 7. -You know what? Let's skip it.
瑞秋，不是约7点吗？ 今天就算了
What? Why?
什么？为什么？
You and your sister seem to have a very special bond
你们兄妹似乎…非常要好
Oh,great. That "special bond" again.
太好了，又说这句话
Why do women have a problem with my being close to my sister?
我跟我妹感情好 又是哪里让女人看不顺眼了？
-I don't know, but..  -Do you have brothers?
听我说，我不知道事实真相 你有兄弟吗？
No,I have two sisters. But one has a very masculine energy.
我有两个妹妹 其中一个很像男人婆
-Are you close? -No. They're not very nice people.
你们要好吗？ 没有，她们不是好人
I like you. I think this could go somewhere.
我很喜欢你 应该可以顺利交往
So I'm close to my family. Don't let it stand in our way.
我是跟家人感情深厚 你就为了这点不鸟我？
Well,I don't know....
我也不知道…
When you put it that way
听你这么说也有道理
Danny? Hurry up. The bath's getting cold.
丹尼 快点 洗澡水快凉了
-What？ -I'll see you later.
又怎么了？ 我先走了
There's some kids playing in the street.
路上有小孩在玩耍
Want to go give them a project, ruin their day?
你要不要去叫他们写作业 毁了他们的一天？
If they have a ball, you could stick razors in it...
如果你手边有球 就可以插上剃刀
...and teach them a new game: "Gonna-Need-Stitches Ball."
教他们玩“杀人球”
Hey,guys! I was at the library. I already finished my five pages.
我整个早上都待在图书馆 已经写完今天的5页了
Now we can go to the Ranger game last night!
那我们可以去看昨晚的骑兵队比赛了
No,dude. Ross tore up the tickets.
不行，门票给罗斯撕掉了
I guess without so many distractions it's easier for you to focus?
没有让你分心的事情 就比较容易专心吧？
Also without somebody breathing down your neck all the livelong day!
没人整天跟在你屁股后面 也比较得心应手吧？
The important thing is, I finished it. And I think it's really good.
随便你们说，总之我写完了 而且写得还不错
But it would help if I could hear it. Would you guys read it for me?
不过你们帮忙念台词 才是帮大忙 可不可以念一下？
-Yeah,all right. -All right.
好吧 好
"It's a typical New York apartment.
“一间普通的纽约公寓”
Two guys are hanging out."
“两个男人正在家里”，罗斯
"Hey,man."
嗨
"What is up?"
有什么事？
"About yesterday. I was really wrong. I am sorry."
昨天是我错了，对不起
"No,it was me. I'm sorry. I overreacted."
我才该道歉，我反应过头了
"Maybe it was both of us. But we had our best friend's inter
或许我们都有错 反正我们都是为了朋友…
But we had our best friend's interest at heart."
我们都是为了朋友好
"Could I be more sorry?"
我非常不好意思
"l don't know. I am one sorry...
我才是该道歉的...
...polontologist."
...古生物学家
All right, Joey, we get it.
乔伊，我们懂了
-I'm sorry. -I'm sorry too.
对不起 我也该道歉
Keep reading. The good part's coming up.
你们要继续读下去 精采的才要上场，继续念
"l am sorry, Chandler."
对不起，钱德
"l am sorry, Ross."
对不起，罗斯
"A handsome man enters."
“帅哥上场”
"l don't know what you're talking about, but I'd like to thank you both.
不知道你们在扯什么 不过我要向你们两位道谢
You. You wouldn't let me give up on myself.
你让我不放弃自己
And you.
你
You co-created Fireball."
你与我一起创造了大火球
"The End."
“剧终”
This took you all day?
这就花了你一整天？
No, this took five minutes.
没有，我只写了5分钟
I spent the rest of the day coming up with new Ultimate Fireball!
其他时间都在写 “终极大火球”游戏规则
It's a typical New York apartment. Two girls are just hanging out. Go.
场景在一般纽约公寓 屋内有两个女生
-"Hi,how are you doing,Kelly?" -"I'm doing just fine.
嗨，凯莉，你好吗？ 我很好
God, Tiffany, you smell so great."
提芬妮，你今天好香
"It's my new perfume.
我喷了新香水
Why don't you come closer where you can really appreciate it?"
你过来一点才闻得仔细
-Joey,you are sick. -This is disgusting.
乔伊，你这大变态 恶毙了
I'm not reading this.
我才不要念哩
Wait,wait,wait! The handsome man was about to enter!
什么？ 等等，帅哥才刚要上场